{
  "shortDescription": "Test your One Piece knowledge!",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Luffy?",
      "answers": ["Pirate", "Marine", "Shogun"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Zoro's weapon?",
      "answers": ["Sword", "Gun", "Axe"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Nami?",
      "answers": ["Navigator", "Cook", "Doctor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the One Piece?",
      "answers": ["Treasure", "Ship", "Island"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Sanji?",
      "answers": ["Cook", "Doctor", "Swordsman"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Going Merry?",
      "answers": ["Ship", "Sword", "Island"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Usopp?",
      "answers": ["Sniper", "Doctor", "Cook"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Devil Fruit?",
      "answers": ["Power", "Fruit", "Weapon"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Chopper?",
      "answers": ["Doctor", "Cook", "Navigator"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Grand Line?",
      "answers": ["Sea", "Ship", "Island"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Robin?",
      "answers": ["Archaeologist", "Cook", "Captain"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Haki?",
      "answers": ["Power", "Weapon", "Island"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Franky?",
      "answers": ["Shipwright", "Cook", "Sniper"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Sunny?",
      "answers": ["Ship", "Island", "Sword"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Brook?",
      "answers": ["Musician", "Cook", "Doctor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Yonko?",
      "answers": ["Emperor", "Ship", "Island"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Jinbe?",
      "answers": ["Fishman", "Marine", "Doctor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Red Line?",
      "answers": ["Land", "Ship", "Sea"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Shanks?",
      "answers": ["Pirate", "Marine", "King"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Log Pose?",
      "answers": ["Compass", "Ship", "Sword"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
